<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>african grey &#8211; Best African Grey Parrots</title>
	<atom:link href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/tag/african-grey/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 09:27:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/cropped-Untitled-2-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>african grey &#8211; Best African Grey Parrots</title>
	<link>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>All You Need To Know About Congo Grey Parrots</title>
		<link>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/congo-grey-parrots/</link>
					<comments>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/congo-grey-parrots/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[greyafrican]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 22:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[african grey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[african grey parrots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[congo grey parrot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[congo grey parrots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[congo grey parrots for sale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grey parrot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://africangreyparrotfarm.com/?p=440</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Feeding your Congo Grey Parrots a balanced diet may also help keep the pet nutritious for decades. Retailer-purchased parrot pellets ought to account for a lot of the foodstuff it eats. In addition to pellets, offer a smaller serving of fresh fruits or veggies in the mornings and evenings to forestall calcium and vitamin A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/congo-grey-parrots/">All You Need To Know About Congo Grey Parrots</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com">Best African Grey Parrots</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Feeding your Congo Grey Parrots a balanced diet may also help keep the pet nutritious for decades. Retailer-purchased parrot pellets ought to account for a lot of the foodstuff it eats. In addition to pellets, offer a smaller serving of fresh fruits or veggies in the mornings and evenings to forestall calcium and vitamin A deficiencies.<br><br>Feather plucking is a common symptom noticed amongst these distressed <strong><a href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/available-parrots/">grey parrots</a></strong>. In addition, they may very well be susceptible to behavioural difficulties because of their sensitive character. Social isolation hastens tension and getting older. Their potential to reproduce noises has resulted in them performing exercises their vocal qualities before people; one example is within the steel band Hatebeak.<br><br>“They don’t appear to be treated very well, and there are actually high rates of mortality that take place at this stage.”<br><br>In South Africa,&nbsp;the last 10 years noticed an increase in captive breeding of Congo grey parrots, but the desire for wild birds has ongoing, Martin described.<br><br>Consider getting ready fruits and veggies otherwise. In case your parrot turns its beak if you give fruits and veggies, it might have a difficulty with how they’re well prepared.<br><br>They are also recognized to come to a decision when to alter their human bonds, which makes it a bit heartbreaking for caregivers who have developed to love their Congo Grey Parrots.<br><br>D’Cruze echoes Martin’s sentiments, inquiring any probable parrot operator these questions: “Have you been ready bodily and mentally to care for this sort of smart, sentient, prolonged-lived wild animal?<br><br>Begin smaller. Don&#8217;t expect them to recite Hamlet suitable off the bat! Instruct them easy phrases like “hi” and “goodbye,” and the moment they&#8217;re comfy with their new vocabulary, start off incorporating the text right into a back again-and-forth dialogue.<br><br>Spot its everyday pellet ration while in the cage. Right after getting rid of the fresh new food each morning, deliver your parrot which has a container of pellet foodstuff. The amount will vary determined by your parrot’s age along with your brand of foodstuff, but the amount should really usually be in between one quarter and 1 fifty percent of a cup (eighty-five to one hundred seventy grams).<br><br>Is there a cup having an interior lip that will prevent this bad habit? It should be a locking cup or she picks it up and spills everything.<br><br>Call us anytime for more info and price, go to <strong><a href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/">our Site</a></strong>.<br>Some investigation has revealed that foot desire can be associated with the number of words a particular Congo Grey Parrot may well know and use. Scientists found that Congo Grey parrots who prefer to employ their proper foot confirmed a marked increase in the number of terms within their lexicon when compared with parrots who were left-footed.<br><br>Greys are really social species and count on a flock-style framework, regardless if lifted in captivity. Simply because they are so depending on another bird inside their flock, considerably in their speech and vocal means is acquired via conversation using the human beings with whom they reside. Equally wild and captive parrots are actually demonstrated to implement. Make contact with phone calls, which permit them to connect with their flock mates and converse details about their spot, detection of predators, availability of meals, and basic safety standing.<br><br>Look for foodstuff dispensing toys on the net or at your dog retail outlet. You might also supply a container with a small degree of seeds combined with pebbles, so your parrot will have to dig to discover its treats.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/congo-grey-parrots/">All You Need To Know About Congo Grey Parrots</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com">Best African Grey Parrots</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/congo-grey-parrots/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the African Grey?</title>
		<link>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/what-is-the-african-grey/</link>
					<comments>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/what-is-the-african-grey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[greyafrican]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 20:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[african grey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[african grey parrot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[african grey parrot for sale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[african greys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grey parrots]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://africangreyparrotfarm.com/?p=433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>African Grey have numerous shades of grey plus the hen has quite distinct red tail feathers. These birds have bare white face patches, black beaks and often brilliant, usually pale, silvery yellow eyes. A lot of the grey contour feathers are edged with white. This gives them a clean, lacy visual appearance. African greys appreciate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/what-is-the-african-grey/">What is the African Grey?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com">Best African Grey Parrots</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>African Grey have numerous shades of grey plus the hen has quite distinct red tail feathers. These birds have bare white face patches, black beaks and often brilliant, usually pale, silvery yellow eyes. A lot of the grey contour feathers are edged with white. This gives them a clean, lacy visual appearance.<br><br>African greys appreciate a sunbath, hence, permitting them out of the cage and placing them out while in the sunlight would also allow them to stretch somewhat.<br><br>Additionally, your <strong><a href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/">parrot</a></strong> may well enjoy fatty or salty foods like potato chips, pizza crusts, and french fries. But you ought to present these sparingly and in small amounts.<br><br>These birds are thought of as Just about the most incredible, helpful, courteous and heat breeds of parrots on the globe. This can be why these birds not only make good Animals but will also stay rather perfectly with other birds.<br><br>How to deal with a pet fowl. Hen manual with every little thing you have to know to deal with your dog chook from chook supplies and meals, to exercise, security and hen wellness care.<br><br>The African Grey is a darker grey than its Congo counterpart, and which has a maroon tail and it has a pink colour about the higher 3rd from the upper mandible.<br><br>Peanuts will not be a secure meal for your personal parrot. These aflatoxins are not going to have an impact on you. Having said that, they are able to have a really bad impact on your parrot. These aflatoxins can produce a little something identified as Aspergillus.<br><br>Much too many people make the hasty conclusion to undertake a parrot with no bearing in mind the one of a kind desires with the respective species and just how long their parrot can live.<br><br>African grey arrives at sexual maturity when they&#8217;re concerning a few and five years previous. They mate for life. In many areas, the birds breed in the course of the dry period; some populations breed 2 times a year. While flocks might nest in loose aggregations, a pair involves its individual tree, exactly where it creates a nest in a very cavity some thirty metres (one hundred toes) off the bottom.<br><br>The truthful truth about African grey parrots is that they&#8217;re Attractive Animals. Actually with the intelligence level that is so supreme; these birds are very comprehension toward their human lover. These birds are very helpful and get the job done quite very well with little ones.<br><br>Neglect and worry may lead to episodes of feather plucking, a harmful neurosis that is hard to appropriate. Dependable breeders won&#8217;t market youthful birds till they will feed on their own. When they discover that talent, there exists an approximately two-thirty day period window—coincident with wild fledgelings’ introduction to the remainder of the flock—for the duration of which it is best to transfer them to new residences.<br><br>Pet Parrots – A higher intelligence can make it hard to retain these birds, and many other parrot species, satisfied. They bond extremely strongly to their entrepreneurs and require lots<br><br>Conduct added testing to find diseases dependant on historical past and Actual physical Test findings: avian polyomavirus and avian chlamydiosis.<br><br>The African Grey Parrot is most likely the most well-liked pet bird and is thought to become the most clever and probably the most talkative of your parrot loved ones.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/what-is-the-african-grey/">What is the African Grey?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://africangreyparrotfarm.com">Best African Grey Parrots</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://africangreyparrotfarm.com/what-is-the-african-grey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
